(Raj:)She is. She's just running a little late.
(Raj:)You know how it is, girls, always fussing
about their hair, their makeup, she'll be here.
(Raj:)Just give it a rest, okay?
(Sheldon:)Can I have your attention, everyone?
That's B-flat for those
who don't have perfect pitch.
(Sheldon:)I would like to propose a toast
to my best friend, Dr. Leonard Hofstadter.
(Sheldon:)He has been presented
with a wonderful opportunity...
(Sheldon:)...and I couldn't be happier for him.
(Leonard:)Thank you, Sheldon,
that must have been hard for you to say.
(Sheldon:)Well, I mean it. I'm really happy for you.
(Sheldon:)And that's how you get
a toothpaste commercial. Cheers.
(Sheldon:)Cheers.
That's really nice of you
to try to be happy for Leonard.
(Leonard:)- Thank you.
- It must've killed you when I went to space.